CORMAC PUJALS

+1 (650) 960-5069 • cmpujals@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/cormacpujals github.com/cormacpujals/ Energetic, resourceful, and reliable software engineer with experience working at fast-paced, solution-oriented companies with a penchant for inquiry, problem-solving, and optimization. Skilled in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, React, Python, and Django.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Immersive

General Assembly, San Francisco, CA

Jul 2022 – Dec 2022

• 420+ hour bootcamp on full stack development

Graduate Study in Economics

University of Leipzig, Leipzig, Germany

Oct 2020 - Jan 2022

• Research and teaching assistant

Bachelor of Arts in Economics, minor in Data Science

San Francisco State University, San Francisco, CA

Sep 2015 - Jan 2019

• Dean's List: every semester | One-year academic exchange at Mannheim University

PROJECTS

NationalParksRock

- Application designed to make discovering and tracking national parks that you want to visit easy and fun
- User-centric SPA built with the MERN-stack. Utilizes JWT tokens for user passwords (All technologies: MongoDB/Mongoose, Express, React, Node, JavaScript, CSS, HTML. Git for version control and Trello, Canva, and LucidChart for project planning and design)

GetTogether

- Community-oriented website created by a team of 3 developers where folks can find local events to attend or post their own
- Full-stack with user-centric CRUD app written in Python/Django.

Bouldering Paradise

- Full stack, user-centric CRUD app designed to offer climbers a way to connect over their shared passion for bouldering
- Technologies used: JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Node, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Git, Trello, Heroku

Spaceman

• Fun and interactive frontend browser game by utilizing JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Github

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Research Analyst

CompNet, Halle, Germany

Sep 2021 – Jan 2022

- Acquired exclusive data from national statistical agencies to understand firm performance across Europe
- Strengthened CompNet's business dynamism research by aggregating and merging firm data into the report
- Led the simplification of our core dataset, easing dataset maintenance and production while increasing its consumption
- Managed CompNet's Twitter account; increased followership by 35% and engagement by nearly 400%

Graduate Student Instructor & Research Assistant

University of Leipzig, Leipzig, Germany

Oct 2020 – Sep 2021

- Assisted the Chair of the Institute for Empirical Research Economics, Professor Dr. Bernd Suessmuth, on three papers, including one that was recently published in <u>Emerging Markets Review</u>
- Enabled success of 250+ native German speaking undergraduate economics students by developing course content and answering questions on our online learning platform

Assistant Director

Planet Granite, San Francisco, CA

May 2015 - May 2020

- Directed a team of 40+ staff, taught climbing technique to 1500+ guests, and processed ~\$1.62M in guest memberships
- Defined standard operating procedures for all employment functions, including customer service, retail, fitness, and safety
- Optimized the point-of-sale UI to maximize front desk efficiency, reducing each customer interaction on average by 10 seconds, resulting in ~60 hours saved each month

Growth Marketing Analyst Intern

CreativeMinds, San Rafael, CA

Aug 2016 – Jan 2017

- Analyzed data from Facebook, Instagram, and websites using R with multiple and univariate linear regression and
 presented key findings to the sales department and management team
- Implemented a software program that automated social media engagement which grew our clients' followership on average by 160%

SKILLS